<resources>
    <!-- General Strings -->
    <string name="app_name">Life Goals</string>
    <string name="enterGoalsPlaceholderText">Enter a goal&#8230;</string>
    <string name="enterGoalsSubmitButtonText">Submit Goals</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="large_text">large text</string>

    <!-- Welcome Strings -->
    <string name="welcomeNext">Next</string>
    <string name="welcomeSkip">Skip</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide1_title">Writing Goals</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide2_title">Goal Setting</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide3_title">Repetition</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide4_title">Target Something, Anything</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide5_title">Stuck for ideas?</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide1_desc">Writing down and visualising your goals is the first step to making them a reality. Hopefully this tool will help you realise your goals, big or small.</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide2_desc">So you have an idea for a goal, is it SMART? Specific, Measurable, Attainable, Relevant, Timely.</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide3_desc">Reciting your goals on a regular basis will help to keep you focused in achieving them.</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide4_desc">Goals can change, whether you achieve a goal, and need a new one, or decide to take your life in another direction. Each day you have a new opportunity to set your goals to guide the direction of your life.</string>
    <string name="welcome_slide5_desc">A good example of a life goal might be: "Organise a camping trip with old friends." The goal doesn\'t have to be world changing, but it does have to be something that would improve your life in either a social, financial, educational way. Now that I have chosen my goal I will write it down, now it\'s one step closer to becoming a reality. Tomorrow i might write it down again, then maybe the day after that. Eventually I might get sick of writing it down and decide to begin planning the trip and before I know it i will be camping with some old friends. See what writing your goals down will do for you.</string>

    <!-- Tutorial Strings -->
    <string name="activity_title_home">Goals</string>
    <string name="msg_no_goals">No entry found!</string>
    <string name="lbl_new_goal_title">New Goal</string>
    <string name="lbl_edit_goal_title">Edit Goal</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_goal">Enter your goal!</string>

    <!-- Button Strings -->
    <string name="clear_entries">Delete All Entries</string>

    <!-- Setting Header Strings -->
    <string name="management">Management</string>
    <string name="preferences">User Preferences</string>


</resources>
